Guide to the Duke Real Estate Office records, 1893-2018 and undated UA.10.04.0007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Real Estate Deeds, 1893-2018; undated
  - File No.: 990, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Warren & Frances Lerner, Type: Deed, 1970 June 11 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #12
  - File No.: 991, Grantee: Athos & Anna Ottolenghi, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 February 28 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #F-9, Comments/Location: Duke Homesite, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 992, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Leon & Pauline Lack, Type: Deed, 1969 September 9 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 993, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Bernard/Pauline Sillberman, Type: Deed, 1972 November 2 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 994, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Richard & Francesca Burns, Type: Deed, 1968 July 9 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 996, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Hamilton & Eleanor Hoyler, Type: Deed, 1969 January 7 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 997, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Harold & Sheila Harris, Type: Deed, 1967 November 6 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 337, Page: 482, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #D-3, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 5/Paid in full
  - File No.: 997, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Harold & Sheila Harris, Type: Deed, 1972 March 3 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 386, Page: 139, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #15, Comments/Location: Duke Homesite, Sec. 7/Paid in full
  - File No.: 998, Grantee: Marcel & Joan Tetel, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 March 15 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 999, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John & Anne H. Heider, Type: Deed, 1968 March 4 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1000, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: George & Eva Somjen, Type: Deed, 1968 August 9 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1002, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Ralph & Patricia Jennings, Type: Deed, 1968 November 5 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #9, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 1003, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Howard & Julia Clark, Type: Deed, 1968 August 26 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #2, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 1004, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. Y. Turner Heirs, Type: Deed, 1968 March 11 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1005, Grantee: Ronald & Emily Chen, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 April 13 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1006, Grantee: Chen, Grantor: Duke, 1968 May 1 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: no deed
  - File No.: 1007, Grantee: David & E. Ruth Lang, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 May 1 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1008, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Stuart & Thelma Sessoms, Type: Deed, 1968 October 31 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #11, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 1009, Grantee: No Deed, undated (Box 17)
    Comments/Location: Letter from Marcel Kinsborne
  - File No.: 1010, Grantee: George C. Myers, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1969 July 1 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #22, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 7/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1011, Grantee: Charles & Gerter Bishop, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 June 10 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1012, Grantee: James A. McFarland, Grantor: Duke, Type: DOT/NOTE, 1968 June 21 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 36, Page: 15, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-10, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 5/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1014, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Orange/Alamance Water Sys., Type: Deed, 1968 January 6 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1015, Grantee: Duke Power Company, Grantor: Duke, Type: ROW, 1968 September 3 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1016, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Daniel C. Tosteson, Type: Deed, 1974 February 12 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 411, Page: 514, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 28,29,30, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 1019, Grantee: Z. Daniel & Carol Pauk, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 October 9 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1020, Grantee: John Boynton, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 October 15 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #32, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 7/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1023, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Wayne & Ann Williams, Type: Deed, 1969 July 1 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #D-3
  - File No.: 1024, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Alan & Gratia Hurlburt, Type: DOT/Note, 1958 May 31 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1027, Grantee: Ben & Jean Weaver, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1969 January 14 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #21, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1030, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Herbert & Joyce Sullivan, Type: Deed, 1969 May 9 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1032, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Luther H. Barbour, Type: Deed, 1969 March 25 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1033, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: M.Black, A.Pope, D.Cates, Type: Deed, 1969 March 25 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1035, Grantee: Letter Only, Grantor: Peregrina C. Labay, 1969 May 23 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: letter only regarding loan
  - File No.: 1037, Grantee: Letter Only, Grantor: Hewlette C. Connell, 1969 July 2 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1038, Grantee: Laney & Lois Funderburke, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1969 July 10 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 51, Page: 95, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #J-3, Comments/Location: Homesite, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1039, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: C. Shelby & Grace Dale, Type: Deed, 1969 March 26 (Box 17)
    County: Martin, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #1,Blks 15-21, Comments/Location: Florida Property
  - File No.: 1040, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: M.G. & Janet Carpenter, Type: Warr/Deed, 1969 July 1 (Box 17)
    County: Carteret
  - File No.: 1045, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Lionel & Mary Griffith, Type: Deed, 1969 May 31 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #6, Blk 12, Comments/Location: 817 Lancaster
  - File No.: 1046, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Franklin & Jean Young, Type: Deed, 1970 August 31 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1047, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: State of North Carolina, Type: Deed, 1969 April 4 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 1048, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thomas & Barbara Harle, Type: Deed, 1970 October 5 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot#H-10, PlBk 51
  - File No.: 1049, Grantee: Calvin L. Ward, Grantor: Duke, undated (Box 17)
    Comments/Location: no deed
  - File No.: 1051, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Ethel M. Cook Lepper, Type: Deed, 1969 November 4 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Will Book #4
  - File No.: 1052, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1969 September 17 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #17, Comments/Location: Sec. 7, Cornwallis Road, 7 acres for Park
  - File No.: 1054, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Daniel/Magdalena Tostison, Type: Deed, 1970 February 5 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 362, Page: 56, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #16, Comments/Location: Homesite, Sec. 7/Returned to Duke
  - File No.: 1056, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sea Level, Type: Deed, 1969 October 1 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1057, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: George R. & Laura Wallace, Type: Deed, 1969 December 17 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1058, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John & Barbara Boineau, Type: Deed, 1970 December 12 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1060, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Wm. Blair, Barbara Anderson, Type: Deed, 1972 December 21 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 396, Page: 777, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #25, Comments/Location: Homesites Sec. 7
  - File No.: 1061, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Marc J. Musser, Jr., 1970 January 21 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 36, Page: 15
  - File No.: 1062, Grantee: Robert O. Friedel, Grantor: Duke, 1970 February 12 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 60, Page: 81
  - File No.: 1063, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Jeff & Mary Steinert, Type: DOT, 1971 May 28 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #C-2, Comments/Location: PB 36/Sold to Shytles-8/22/74-Paid in Full
  - File No.: 1067, Grantee: Robert & Nancy Brame, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1970 May 6 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1069, Grantee: Martin & Anne Black, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1970 May 6 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sea Level, Type: Deed, 1971 January 28 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: RW & MS Postlethwait, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1971 January 13 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sea Level, Type: Deed, 1971 January 4 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: Sea Level, Grantor: State of NC, Type: Cert/Incor, 1952 July 30 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: Sea Level, Grantor: Taylor Foundation, Type: Deed/Gift, 1957 November 14 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: Sea Level, Grantor: State of NC, 1962 April 26 (Box 18)
    County: Carteret, Comments/Location: Articles of Amendment to Sea Level
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Harold Peacock (Heirs), Type: Deed, 1970 September 30 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: Sea Level, Grantor: Taylor Foundation, Type: Deed, 1953 November 16 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: DE & Frances Taylor, Type: Deed, 1971 January 28 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1071, Grantee: Sea Level, Grantor: West India Fruit, Type: Deed, 1964 March 12 (Box 18)
    County: Carteret, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 5,6,7 & C
  - File No.: 1072, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Battle, Joseph and Thelma, Type: Deed, 1971 July 29 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 379, Page: 358, Map-Block-Lot: 236-02-015, Comments/Location: Homesite, Sec 7/ Lots 28, 29,30 now owned by Roberts
  - File No.: 1073, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Norman & Annette Kirshner, Type: Deed, 1972 November 2 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1074, Grantee: EB & Priscilla Palmore, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1970 December 1 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #18, Comments/Location: Homesite, Sec. 7/Sold to Fritz Klein/1980
  - File No.: 1076, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Edna Jackson, Type: Deed, 1970 December 16 (Box 18)
    County: Carteret, Comments/Location: Plat Book 59 - page 15
  - File No.: 1077, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Richard & Nadine Burton, Type: Deed, 1971 March 9 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1080, Grantee: Merel & Armide Harmel, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1971 April 1 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1082, Grantee: James,Jerrie Charlesworth, Grantor: Duke, Type: DOT, 1972 November 24 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #27, Comments/Location: Duke Homesite, Sec VII/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1083, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Moo-Young & Chang Han, Type: DOT, 1978 August 19 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Paid
  - File No.: 1084, Grantee: Harry A. & Phyllis Owen, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1971 September 10 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #18, Comments/Location: Paid
  - File No.: 1088, Grantee: Hester & Gertrude Germain, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1972 January 4 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #14, 6, Comments/Location: Durham County Tax Map 107
  - File No.: 1089, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: R.H. Michaux for E. Leper, Type: Deed, 1972 January 11 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 4, Page: 63, Comments/Location: WILL
  - File No.: 1090, Grantee: N.C. Corp-Rbts. Const Co, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1972 March 27 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 16-17,29-30,23, Comments/Location: Block A, Plat Book 6/Sec 2 Univ. Heights
  - File No.: 1094, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Bessie H. Hilliard, Type: Deed, 1972 June 9 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 4-5, Comments/Location: Plat Book 1/909-911 Wilkerson Avenue
  - File No.: 1095, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Viola Montgomery, Type: DOT, 1972 June 8 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: -654624
  - File No.: 1096, Grantee: Richard & Barbara Peck, Grantor: Duke, Type: DOT/Note, 1973 July 12 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 880, Page: 442, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #7, Comments/Location: Homesite, Sec. 8/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1097, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dale R. & Sybil Lindsay, Type: Deed, 1972 April 7 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 387, Page: 381, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #12, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 7
  - File No.: 1099, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: D.C. May Co., Inc., Type: Deed, 1972 June 27 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1103, Grantee: Herbert & Julie Aikens, Grantor: Duke, 1972 August 18 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #3, Comments/Location: Block C
  - File No.: 1107, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Alan & M. E. Marchester, Type: Deed, 1972 August 31 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Plat Book 9, Page 59
  - File No.: 1108, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Walter & Barbara Taylor, Type: Deed, 1972 October 25 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1109, Grantee: Rbt.& Valentina Hartford, Grantor: Duke, Type: DOT/Note, 1973 January 19 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #42, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 2/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1110, Grantee: Durham Health Care, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1977 September 2 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1010 Broad Street, Family Medicine
  - File No.: 1116, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Asheville Christ. Academy, Type: Deed, 1973 February 22 (Box 18)
    County: Buncombe, Comments/Location: Highland Hospital
  - File No.: 1119, Grantee: Wilma Johnston Parham, Grantor: Duke, Type: QC/Deed, 1977 May 23 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #8, BlkB, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1120, Grantee: State of N.C., Grantor: Duke, Type: Easement, 1973 May 22 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Old/New File No.: 3047
  - File No.: 1123, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Homeco, Inc., Type: Deed, 1973 August 27 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: -609214, Comments/Location: Pickett Road, Lizzie Teer Pickett
  - File No.: 1124, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Adella S. Parks, Type: Deed, 1973 August 30 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1707 Bynum Street
  - File No.: 1125, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Mrs. Rupert Wilkerson, Type: Deed, 1974 February 18 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 411, Page: 739, Map-Block-Lot: 150-1-11,12, Comments/Location: 831-833 Wilkerson/sold 831 on 8/11/93
  - File No.: 1125, Grantee: N. C. Comm. Land Trustees, Grantor: Duke, 1993 August 11 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 831 Wilkerson
  - File No.: 1126, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: C.A. Ricca, Type: Deed, 1973 December 26 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 834 Wilkerson & 921 Rome (Spring) & 509 Gattis;Burch Ave. Proj.
  - File No.: 1127, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: C. M. Montgomery, Type: Deed, 1973 December 17 (Box 18)
  - File No.: 1128, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Durham City Bd Educ, Type: Deed, 1973 September 11 (Box 18)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Crest School
  - File No.: 1130, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Haywood Roberts, etc., Type: Deed, 1974 September 14 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1132, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: E. P. Grant, Type: Deed, 1974 September 6 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 309 Oregon Street
  - File No.: 1133, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Floy T. Gibson, Type: Deed, 1974 September 6 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 16-17, Comments/Location: 509 Gattis Street; Burch Ave. Housing Project
  - File No.: 1136, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Harry Ebert, 1976 February 13 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1136, Grantee: Dr. Frank Baker, Grantor: Duke, 1976 February 24 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1136, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dr. Frank Baker, 1976 May 26 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1136, Grantee: Dr. Richard L. Cox, Grantor: Duke, Type: DOT/Note, 1976 September 9 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #D-19, Comments/Location: Homesite, Sec. 5, Paid in full
  - File No.: 1142, Grantee: G. A. Lazarus, Grantor: Duke, Type: DOT/Note, 1975 August 15 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 911, Page: 876, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #8, Comments/Location: Homesite, Sec. 7/Paid in full
  - File No.: 1142, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dr. & Mrs. G. S. Lazarus, Type: Loan, 1975 August 22 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1151, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Betty Dumaine, Type: Deed/Gift, 1976 December 5 (Box 19)
    County: Moore
  - File No.: 1152, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sailor's Snug Harbor, Type: Deed, 1976 January 19 (Box 19)
    County: Carteret, Comments/Location: Sea Level, NC
  - File No.: 1152, Grantee: Carolina DOT, Grantor: Duke, Type: Quitclaim, 1982 September 20 (Box 19)
    County: Carteret, Comments/Location: Quitclaim Deed - North
  - File No.: 1153, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: W. Horace Corbett, Type: Two, 1975 January 3 (Box 19)
    County: N. Hanov., Comments/Location: Wilmington, NC; New Hanover; 2 Deeds
  - File No.: 1154, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Ruby M. Drakeford, Type: Deed, 1976 June 22 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 303 Case Street (lot)
  - File No.: 1155, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: R. B. Cooke Property, Type: Deeds, 1974 May 1 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Case & Hull Streets; 3 Deeds;School for Children?
  - File No.: 1155, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, 1976 August 6 (Box 19)
    County: Duham, Comments/Location: FILE MISSING, Old/New File No.: 3057
  - File No.: 1156, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Zadie J. Riley Estate, Type: Deed, 1976 July 13 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 301 Case Street (lot)
  - File No.: 1157, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Curtis & Margaret Smithdeal, 1976 November 15 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1157, Grantee: Lewis G. Ferreti, Grantor: Duke, 1977 December 22 (Box 19)
    Map-Block-Lot: Lot #1, Map 5, Comments/Location: Willow Creek, High Point, NC, FILE MISSING
  - File No.: 1158, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. E. Wall/Roberts Const. Co., Type: Trus/Deed, 1976 July 30 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Tax Map 38-7-3, Comments/Location: 712 Wilkerson; 813, 815, 819 Pettigrew
  - File No.: 1158, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Home Builders' Supply, Type: Deed, 1976 July 30 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1158, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Roberts Const. Co., Type: QC/Deed, 1976 July 30 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1159, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. Pickett, I. Bridger, Type: Deed, 1976 November 12 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites
  - File No.: 1161, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sophia S. Cody, Type: Deed, 1976 December 12 (Box 19)
    County: Watauga
  - File No.: 1162, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Mountreal, Inc., Type: Deed, 1975 December 18 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1163, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: LD Corporation, Type: Deed, 1974 May 25 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1164, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: LD Corporation, Type: Deed, 1974 May 25 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1165, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Robert E. Cooper, Type: QC/Deed, 1975 December 8 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1166, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Ottis T. Williams, Type: Deed, 1977 April 4 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Tax Map 107-7-2, Comments/Location: 309 Anderson Avenue
  - File No.: 1168, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: E. M. Williams, Type: License, 1977 August 29 (Box 19)
    County: Lee, Comments/Location: 2 lots; Sanford, NC
  - File No.: 1168, Grantee: Dennis Womack, Grantor: Duke, 1977 December 28 (Box 19)
    County: Lee
  - File No.: 1169, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thor Hall, Type: Deed, 1976 March 1 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1170, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: City of Durham, Type: Deed, 1976 June 1 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 924, Page: 358-360, Comments/Location: Rowan Street
  - File No.: 1172, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thomas & Dawn Naylor, Type: War/Deed, 1977 December 20 (Box 19)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Birchwood Lake Estates, Lot 14 & 15
  - File No.: 1173, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: City of Durham, Type: Deed, 1978 May 11 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 971, Page: 645, Comments/Location: Plat Book 84, Page 37, 7.01 acres
  - File No.: 1175, Grantee: Jim Tucker et al, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1978 June 21 (Box 19)
    County: Cabarrus, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 55,65,79,83, Comments/Location: Carolando Subdiv. Sec 2/fr: E&Mary Morris
  - File No.: 1177, Grantee: Andrew Collins, etc., Grantor: Duke, Type: War/Deed, 1978 May 31 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: -606298, Comments/Location: Hwy 751-Chapel Hill Road
  - File No.: 1178, Grantee: State of N.C., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed/Gift, 1978 August 19 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1179, Grantee: Paul A. Robell, Grantor: Duke, Type: Rlse/Deed, 1978 September 28 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: 723 Anderson St, Comments/Location: Release of reversionary interest
  - File No.: 1182, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: James Poe, Type: War/Deed, 1978 October 9 (Box 19)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Campus Service Print Shop; 2707 Edmund St.
  - File No.: 1183, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Bill Pinna, Type: Deed, 1976 December 22 (Box 19)
    County: Transyl., Comments/Location: 2 Acres; Transylvania County, NC
  - File No.: 1184, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Cameron Brown, Type: Trus/Deed, 1978 September 5 (Box 19)
    County: Wake, Comments/Location: Riverbend
  - File No.: 1186, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Israel Freedman, Type: Gift, 1978 December 12 (Box 19)
    County: Granville, Deed Book: 222, Page: 814, Comments/Location: 158.116 acres on SR 1410
  - File No.: 1188, Grantee: Teray & Margaret Sanford, Grantor: Duke, 1978 October 30 (Box 19)
    Comments/Location: Bruton Road
  - File No.: 1189, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John Shytle, 1978 December 19 (Box 19)
    County: Georgetown, Comments/Location: 4 lots; Georgetown County in South Carolina
  - File No.: 1190, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dr. Peter Scardino, 1976 December 22 (Box 19)
    County: Wautauga, Comments/Location: Charter Hills, Beech Mountain
  - File No.: 1191, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Z. B. Newton, III, Type: Gift, 1976 December 30 (Box 19)
    County: Cumberland, Comments/Location: 1 acre, Rockfish Township, Crest Hill
  - File No.: 1192, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Hilliard Eure, 1978 December 29 (Box 19)
    County: Wautauga, Comments/Location: Lot 159, Creekridge, Beech Mountain
  - File No.: 1197, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: V.C. Corporation, Type: QC/Deed, 1979 May 25 (Box 19)
  - File No.: 1198, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: V.C. Corporation, Type: QC/Deed, 1979 May 25 (Box 19)
    County: Guilford
  - File No.: 1199, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: V.C. Corporation, Type: QC/Deed, 1979 May 25 (Box 19)
    County: Dur-Wake
  - File No.: 1200, Southland Associates, Grantor: Duke, 1971 October 10 (Box 20)
  - File No.: 1201, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, 1979 January 16 (Box 20)
  - File No.: 1203, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, 1979 August 24 (Box 20)
  - File No.: 1204, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: The Continental Group, Type: War/Deed, 1979 December 13 (Box 20)
    County: Wake, Deed Book: 2793, Page: 785-786, Map-Block-Lot: 284-00284-0009, Comments/Location: Riverbend - Hindsdale Tract
  - File No.: 1205, Grantee: Hotel Feasability Study, Grantor:, 1979 December 27 (Box 20)
  - File No.: 1206, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Cameron-Brown Company, Type: War/Deed, 1979 July 6 (Box 20)
    County: Wake, Deed Book: 2746, Page: 513-514, Comments/Location: Quail Professional Center
  - File No.: 1207, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Helen G. Swift, Type: War/Deed, 1979 December 7 (Box 20)
    County: Sarasota, Page: 977762-3, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 2-3, Comments/Location: Siesta Properties, Florida
  - File No.: 1209, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sea Level Dev. Co., Inc., Type: War/Deed, 1969 October 1 (Box 20)
    County: Carteret, Deed Book: 315, Page: 29, Comments/Location: Land
  - File No.: 1209, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sea Level Gen./Child. Hosp, Type: War/Deed, 1969 May 29 (Box 20)
    County: Carteret, Deed Book: 312, Page: 188, Comments/Location: Hospital
  - File No.: 1209, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sea Level Gen./Child. Hosp, Type: War/Deed, 1969 May 29 (Box 20)
    County: Carteret, Comments/Location: Land
  - File No.: 1210, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John C. and Anne W. Russell, Type: Gft/Deed, 1980 December 31 (Box 20)
    County: Guilford, Deed Book: 3124, Page: 759-760, Map-Block-Lot: Lot 12, Sec. 1B, Comments/Location: Pleasant Ridge Estates
  - File No.: 1211, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John C. and Judith E. Glenn, Type: Gft/Deed, 1980 December 30 (Box 20)